<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Disaster First Aid</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Disaster First Aid</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Welcome</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="Emergency_activity">Emergencies</string>
    <string name="mouthpiece">A pocket mask or pocket face mask or CPR mask is a device used to safely deliver rescue breaths during
        a cardiac arrest or respiratory arrest(can be obtained from a loacal red cross.</string>
    <string name="blanket">A blanket van be used to extiguish fire around some object or can be used in cold.</string>
    <string name="flash_light">Falsh light is important in case your accident occurs at night or the disaster also shuts down the
        power.Sometimes accidents happen in the dark(like you are on camping trip and you get mauled by a bear in night.</string>
    <string name="gloves">The first thing you need in your First Aid kit should be your gloves.When we think about gloves in first
        aid kit, we think about blood. We wear gloves to protect ourselves from all body fluids which are all capanle of transferring diseases.</string>
    <string name="tooth">Kids who lose a baby tooth would not need it replaced. But when an older child or teen loses a permanent
        tooth, its a dental emergency.If a tooth preservation kit or a container filled with BSS is not available,
        a knocked out tooth can be put in a container of milk or saliva of your child for transport.</string>
    <string name="thermometer">A first-aid kit should contain a thermometer to measure body tempreture. An oral digital thermometer
        is probably the best choice.Digital thermomteres used in ear are more accurate but also a little expensive.</string>
    <string name="calamine">Calamine is main ingredient in calamine lotion and is used as an antipruritic to treat sun burn,
        eczema, rashes,poison ivy, chicken pox, nsect bites, or sting. It is used as a mild antiseptic to prevent
        infections that can be caused by scratching the affected area.</string>
    <string name="cold">Instant Cold Compress temporarily relieves minor pain and swelling for sprains, strains, aches,
        bruising and sore joints. The urgent first aid instant cold packs are conveniently disposable with no
        pre-chilling required for quick, effective relief.No messy ice bags needed.Just shake, squeeze,
        shake again and apply for instant cool comfort and treatment of injuries.</string>
    <string name="pins">Safety pins are commonly used to fasten pieces of fabric or clothing together.Safety
        pins are usually a special version with extra safe cover.</string>
    <string name="scissors">While the most common use of scissors is for cutting gauze and sometimes even adhesive
        bandages to an appropriate length.It is also used for other tasks such as cutting away
        clothing to expose injured areas to be able to treat wounds better.</string>
    <string name="aceto">Adding Acetaminopheb to non steroidal anti flammatory drugs (NSAIDs), can be effective way to pain relief.</string>
    <string name="hydro">Hydrocortisone is a typical steroid. It reduces the actions of chemicals in the body
        that cause inflammation, redness and swelling. it is typically used to treat inflammation of skin caused
        by number of conditions such as allergic reactions, eczema or psoriasis.</string>
    <string name="antiseptic">Antiseptic Liquid(povidone-iodine) is a potent typical used to prevent to treat infection in minor
        wounds. It is effective at killing bacteria, viruses, fungi, protozoa, molds and yeast.</string>
    <string name="antibiotic">Polymixin B Sulphate-Bacitracin zinc-Gramicidin contains a combination of antibiotics used
        for the treatment of certain types of infetions caused by bacteria. The typical oinment can be used to treat
        certain skin infections such as infected wounds, burns, skin grafts, boils and acne.</string>
    <string name="gauge">Sterile gauze is used for absorbing fluids as well as dressing and protecting wounds. Sterile
        gauze acts as a barrier to prevent contaminants from entering any wound area that it covers
        and absorbs any blood or fluid that seeps out of the wound.</string>
    <string name="tape">Surgical tape or medical tape is a type of pressure-sensitive adhesive tape used in medicine
        and first aid to hold a bandage or other dressing onto a wound.</string>
    <string name="bandages">An adhesive bandage, also called a sticking plaster(or simply plaster)in British English,
        is a small medical dressing used for injuries not serious enough to require a full-size bandage.
        They are also known by the genericized trademarks Band-Aid (as "band-aid" or "band aid" in the US) or
        Elastoplast(in the UK).</string>
    <string name="eleastic">An elastic bandage is a "stretchable bandage used to create localized pressure".
        Elastic bandages are commonly used to treat muscle sprains and strains by reducing the flow of blood to
        a particular area by the application of even stable pressure which can restrict swelling at the place of injury.</string>
    <string name="splint">Casts and splints are hard wraps used to support and protect injured bones, ligaments, tendons
        and other tissues. They help broken bones heal by keeping the broken ends together and as straight as possible.
        Casts and splints also help relieve pain and swelling, and protect the injured area from more harm.</string>
    <string name="wipes">alcohol wipes are designed to clean and for the convenient disinfection of smaller surfaces
        and individual non invasive medical devices.</string>
</resources>
